<Alloy>
	<Window navTintColor="#CE1D1C" title="About PLUX" id="win" class="container" layout="vertical"> 
		    <View layout="vertical">
			    <View layout="horizontal" height="50" width="100%" backgroundColor="#DEDEDE" platform="android"> 
					<View left="0" width="10%">
			         	<ImageView left='10' id="btnBack" width="25" height="25" image="/images/btn-back.png" />
			   		</View>
			     	<View id="pageTitle" width="Ti.UI.FILL">
			     		<Label height="Ti.UI.SIZE" class='normal_font' textAlign="center">About PLUX</Label>
			     	</View> 
			 	</View> 
				<ScrollView id="main" layout="vertical" height="100%" contentHeight="Ti.UI.SIZE">
					<View class=" wfill horz" height="95"  >
						<ImageView borderRadius="10" width="80" height="80" left="10" top="10" image="/images/logo_plux.png" />
						<View class="vert wfill hsize" left="10" top="10">
							<Label class=" themeColor wfill h4 bold left-align">PLUX</Label>
							<Label class=" wfill h5 left-align">Version 1.1.8</Label>
							<Label class=" wfill h5 left-align">Copyright ©2016. All Rights Reserved.</Label>
						</View> 
						
					</View> 
					
					<Label class="description_content" top="10"  >Plux is an app by ASP Medical Group that is reinventing the way companies manage their health care benefits programmes.</Label>
					<Label class="description_content" bottom="5">The ASP Medical Group is committed to improving the quality of health care through the use of technology. Our expertise is in providing comprehensive, hassle-free support for corporate medical benefit programmes. Hundreds of companies have already benefitted from our powerful employee medical benefit administration system, which makes cashless consultations available at a network of over 1000 clinics in Malaysia via our comprehensive claim management service.</Label>
			
					<Label class="description_content" bottom="5">Now, we are making administrating corporate health care programmes even simpler, with Plux.</Label>
					<Label class="description_content" bottom="5">Plux is a FREE app that automates most of the management, claims and tracking functions that are performed by companies’ HR departments. Plux also helps employees keep track of their own medical claims with just a few taps on their smartphones. In addition, Plux members enjoy amazing convenience at their fingertips – they can speak to doctors live via video, as well as access tips and tools to help them manage their health and feel good every day!</Label>	
					
					<Label class="title_header" top="10">FEATURES:</Label>
					 
					<Label class="description_content" bottom="3">- for the maintenance of customer database and customer service related processes;</Label>  
					<View class="horz wfill hsize" left="10"   bottom="3">
						<Label class="description_content themeColor bold hsize  wfill">- Save Time</Label>  
						<Label class="description_content hsize" >Plux takes the pain out of administering a medical benefits programme! No more paper forms, manual claims, or calling the doctor. Much of the paperwork is automated with Plux.</Label>  
					</View>
					
					
					<View class="horz wfill hsize" left="10"   bottom="3">
						<Label class="description_content themeColor bold hsize wfill">- Save Money</Label>  
						<Label class="description_content hsize" >Plux powerful back-end support automates much of the administration process involved in medical benefits programmes, freeing up company resources that can be used more effectively elsewhere.</Label>  
					</View>
					
					<View class="horz wfill hsize" left="10"   bottom="3">
						<Label class="description_content themeColor bold hsize wfill">- Smart Claims Tracking</Label>  
						<Label class="description_content hsize" >Plux members can keep track of their benefits entitlements via their smartphone so that they can manage their claim levels themselves. Access details of entitlements, claims made, claims remaining, etc.</Label>  
					</View>
					
					<View class="horz wfill hsize" left="10"   bottom="3">
						<Label class="description_content themeColor bold hsize wfill">- Convenient Live Virtual Consults</Label>  
						<Label class="description_content hsize" >Plux members can connect with any doctor in the ASP Medical Group via video for an affordable pay-as-you-go fee. Doctors can then decide on the best course of action for the employee immediately. This way, employees can get medical advice from doctors without having to take time off to wait at the doctor’s clinic.</Label>  
					</View>
				 
				  	<View class="horz wfill hsize" left="10"   bottom="3">
						<Label class="description_content themeColor bold hsize wfill">- Simple Doctor Appointment Booking</Label>  
						<Label class="description_content hsize" >Plux members can easily book appointments with any doctor in the ASP Medical Group via their mobile phones. Employees can choose from a panel of thousands of doctors for unparalleled convenience.</Label>  
					</View>
					
					<View class="horz wfill hsize" left="10"   bottom="3">
						<Label class="description_content themeColor bold hsize wfill">- Easy Clinic Locator</Label>  
						<Label class="description_content hsize" >Plux members can easily search for a clinic closest to them through our comprehensive clinic listing. Search through our panel of thousands of doctors, located all over Malaysia.</Label>  
					</View>
					 
					<View class="horz wfill hsize" left="10"   bottom="3">
						<Label class="description_content themeColor bold hsize wfill">- Powerful Health Checklists</Label>  
						<Label class="description_content hsize" >Every Plux member has access to health checklists that help them manage their own health goals. Healthier employees translates to happier and more productive employees. It also means less resources spent on therapy.</Label>  
					</View>
					
					<View class="horz wfill hsize" left="10"   bottom="3">
						<Label class="description_content themeColor bold hsize wfill">- Personalized Health Tracking</Label>  
						<Label class="description_content hsize" >A personal digital map of health and well-being is automatically created for all Plux members, so they are aware if their lifestyles needs to change to become healthier.</Label>  
					</View>
					
					<View class="horz wfill hsize" left="10"   bottom="3">
						<Label class="description_content themeColor bold hsize wfill">- Health tips delivered regularly</Label>  
						<Label class="description_content hsize" >Plux members receive health news tips to help them make better lifestyle choices and stay healthy.</Label>  
					</View>
					
					<View class="horz wfill hsize" left="10"   bottom="3">
						<Label class="description_content themeColor bold hsize wfill">- IT’S FREE</Label>  
						<Label class="description_content hsize" >Companies and members get all the benefits of this powerful app at no charge!</Label>  
					</View>
				 

					 
				</ScrollView>
			</View>
		 
	</Window>
</Alloy>